CURRICULUM VITAE OF KATLEHO MPHEQEKE



CAREER GOALS:

I aspire to constantly grow in my field and broaden my perspective as well as my knowledge by learning from the people around me and in my team. I'm motivated to work my way up and hopefully in 10 years' time be promoted into senior position

PERSONAL DETAILS:

Surname: Mpheqeke

Name: Katleho

Identity number: 9805305259080

Age: 22

Gender: Male

Nationality: South-African

Home language: Sotho

Residential Address: 50 Faraday Boulevard,

Vanderbijlpark,

Gauteng,

1911

Contact number: 0658175027 / 0731605551

Email address: mpheqekek@gmail.com

LinkdIn Profile: https://www.linkedin.com/in/katleho-mphegeke-3321a9197/

EDUCATION, TRAINING AND QUALIFICATIONS:

1. Institution: North-West University

Degree: Bachelor of Science in Information Technology

Year: 2020

Major Subjects: Object Orientated Programming, Communication Skills, System

Analysis, Information Security, Data Structures and Algorithms, Data Analytics, Structured Programming, User Interface Programming, Databases, Decision Support Systems, Artificial Intelligence,

Computer Networks

2. Highest Grade passed: 12

School: Hoërskool Transvalia

Year: 2016

SHORT COURSES ATTENDED:

INSTITUTION: Udemy

COURSE: Windows Passwords and Account hacking.

Web Design for Beginners: Real World Coding in HTML & CSS.

Learn Ethical Hacking from Scratch.

Plan, Plig, Plons en Plas vaardigheidsopleiding vir 2014 se graad 10 en 11, FAMSA VAAL TRAINGLE

WORK EXPERIENCE

1. Institution: North-West University Vanderbijlpark Campus

Section: Faculty of Natural and Agricultural Science

Period: 05 Feb 2018 – 30 Jun 2018, 03 Aug 2018–19 Oct 2018

Position: Student Assistant (Semester Appointment/ Part time Contract)

Duties: Assisting lecturer during class with students,

Tutoring students on algorithms and programming skills,

Marking assessments and capturing marks on student portal(efundi),

Offering technical support with laptops where needed.

2. Institution: North-West University Vanderbijlpark Campus

Section: Faculty of Natural and Agricultural Science

Period: 04 Feb 2019–30 May 2019, 01 Jul 2019–01 Nov 2019

Position: Student Assistant (Semester Appointment/ Part time Contract)

Duties: Assisting lecturer during class with students,

Tutoring students on algorithms and programming skills,

Marking assessments and capturing marks on student portal(efundi),

Offering technical support with laptops where needed.

3. Institution: North-West University Vanderbijlpark Campus

Section: Faculty of Natural and Agricultural Science

Period: 04 Feb 2020 - Present

Position: Student Assistant (Semester Appointment/ Part time Contract)

Duties: Assisting lecturer during class with students,

Tutoring students on algorithms and programming skills,

Marking assessments and capturing marks on student portal(efundi),

Offering technical support with laptops where needed.

VOLUNTEER WORK:

I have worked as a co-worker at Evangelic Lutheran Church during kid's week in 2012, 2013 and 2015

SKILLS and INTERESTS:

Skills:

Programming in various languages such as Delphi, Java, Python, C#, C++, and HTML.

Exceptional problem-solving skills as well as teamwork.

Exceptional communication skills in Afrikaans, English, and Sotho

Interests:

Cybersecurity, Data warehousing, artificial intelligence security bots and automated functions.

Rugby

POSITION OF RESPONSIBILITY:

Prefect at Hoërskool Transvalia 2015 and 2016, as well as class prefect from 2013 to 2016.

REFRENCES:

 Name: Dr Sunè van Der Linde Institution: North West University Position: Subject Chair Vaal

Tel no: 0169103258

2. Name: Mrs Tanja Eksteen Institution: North West University

Position: Lecturer Tel no: 016103285

3. Name: Mss Irma Myburgh Institution: North West University Position: Administrative Officer

Tel no: 0169103288

4. Name: Mr Ruvaun Olivier
 Institution: Hoërskool Transvalia
 Position: Deputy Principal
 Tel no: 016932115/6